  export const conheciementosGerais = [
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "According%20to%20the%20BBPA%2C%20what%20is%20the%20most%20common%20pub%20name%20in%20the%20UK%3F",
      correct_answer: "Red%20Lion",
      incorrect_answers: ["Royal%20Oak", "White%20Hart", "King%27s%20Head"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20does%20a%20milliner%20make%20and%20sell%3F",
      correct_answer: "Hats",
      incorrect_answers: ["Shoes", "Belts", "Shirts"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "In%20a%20standard%20set%20of%20playing%20cards%2C%20which%20is%20the%20only%20king%20without%20a%20moustache%3F",
      correct_answer: "Hearts",
      incorrect_answers: ["Spades", "Diamonds", "Clubs"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20name%20represents%20the%20letter%20%22M%22%20in%20the%20NATO%20phonetic%20alphabet%3F",
      correct_answer: "Mike",
      incorrect_answers: ["Matthew", "Mark", "Max"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Rolex%20is%20a%20company%20that%20specializes%20in%20what%20type%20of%20product%3F",
      correct_answer: "Watches",
      incorrect_answers: ["Cars", "Computers", "Sports%20equipment"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Scotch%20whisky%20and%20Drambuie%20make%20up%20which%20cocktail%3F",
      correct_answer: "Rusty%20Nail",
      incorrect_answers: ["Screwdriver", "Sex%20on%20the%20Beach", "Manhattan"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "In%20the%20Morse%20code%2C%20which%20letter%20is%20indicated%20by%203%20dots%3F%20",
      correct_answer: "S",
      incorrect_answers: ["O", "A", "C"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "Which%20language%20is%20NOT%20Indo-European%3F",
      correct_answer: "Hungarian",
      incorrect_answers: ["Russian", "Greek", "Latvian"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Ivy%20League%20universities%20has%20its%20official%20motto%20in%20Hebrew%20as%20well%20as%20in%20Latin%3F",
      correct_answer: "Yale%20University",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Princeton%20University",
        "Harvard%20University",
        "Columbia%20University",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20very%20first%20video%20uploaded%20to%20YouTube%3F",
      correct_answer: "Me%20at%20the%20zoo",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "tribute",
        "carrie%20rides%20a%20truck",
        "Her%20new%20puppy%20from%20great%20grandpa%20vern.",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",
      correct_answer: "%2412.7%20Billion",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "%2495%20Million",
        "%24956%20Million",
        "%242.7%20Billion",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20companies%20does%20NOT%20manufacture%20automobiles%3F",
      correct_answer: "Ducati",
      incorrect_answers: ["Nissan", "GMC", "Fiat"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Who%20is%20a%20co-founder%20of%20music%20streaming%20service%20Spotify%3F",
      correct_answer: "Daniel%20Ek",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Sean%20Parker",
        "Felix%20Miller",
        "Michael%20Breidenbruecker",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20buildings%20is%20example%20of%20a%20structure%20primarily%20built%20in%20the%20Art%20Deco%20architectural%20style%3F",
      correct_answer: "Niagara%20Mohawk%20Building",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Taipei%20101",
        "One%20Detroit%20Center",
        "Westendstrasse%201",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20alcoholic%20drink%20is%20mainly%20made%20from%20juniper%20berries%3F",
      correct_answer: "Gin",
      incorrect_answers: ["Vodka", "Rum", "Tequila"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20did%20the%20Spanish%20autonomous%20community%20of%20Catalonia%20ban%20in%202010%2C%20that%20took%20effect%20in%202012%3F",
      correct_answer: "Bullfighting",
      incorrect_answers: ["Fiestas", "Flamenco", "Mariachi"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20Italian%20automobile%20manufacturer%20gained%20majority%20control%20of%20U.S.%20automobile%20manufacturer%20Chrysler%20in%202011%3F",
      correct_answer: "Fiat",
      incorrect_answers: ["Maserati", "Alfa%20Romeo", "Ferrari"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20these%20is%20the%20name%20of%20a%20Japanese%20system%20of%20alternative%20medicine%2C%20literally%20meaning%20%22finger%20pressure%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Shiatsu",
      incorrect_answers: ["Ukiyo", "Majime", "Ikigai"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20name%20given%20to%20Indian%20food%20cooked%20over%20charcoal%20in%20a%20clay%20oven%3F",
      correct_answer: "Tandoori",
      incorrect_answers: ["Biryani", "Pani%20puri", "Tiki%20masala"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20German%20word%20for%20%22spoon%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "L%C3%B6ffel",
      incorrect_answers: ["Gabel", "Messer", "Essst%C3%A4bchen"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20romanized%20Japanese%20word%20for%20%22university%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Daigaku",
      incorrect_answers: ["Toshokan", "Jimusho", "Shokudou"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20Swedish%20word%20for%20%22window%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "F%C3%B6nster",
      incorrect_answers: ["H%C3%A5l", "Sk%C3%A4rm", "Ruta"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20romanized%20Russian%20word%20for%20%22winter%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "Zima",
      incorrect_answers: ["Leto", "Vesna", "Osen%27"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20country%20saw%20a%20world%20record%20315%20million%20voters%20turn%20out%20for%20elections%20on%20May%2020%2C%201991%3F",
      correct_answer: "India",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "United%20States%20of%20America",
        "Soviet%20Union",
        "Poland",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "According%20to%20the%20United%20States%27%20CDC%2C%20one%20in%20how%20many%20Americans%20die%20annually%20due%20to%20smoking%3F",
      correct_answer: "Five",
      incorrect_answers: ["Twenty", "Ten", "One%20hundred"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20is%20a%20dead%20mall%3F",
      correct_answer:
        "A%20mall%20with%20high%20vacancy%20rates%20or%20low%20consumer%20foot%20traffic",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "A%20mall%20with%20no%20stores",
        "A%20mall%20that%20has%20been%20condemed",
        "A%20mall%20after%20business%20hours",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20last%20letter%20of%20the%20Greek%20alphabet%3F",
      correct_answer: "Omega",
      incorrect_answers: ["Mu", "Epsilon", "Kappa"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Amsterdam%20Centraal%20station%20is%20twinned%20with%20what%20station%3F",
      correct_answer: "London%20Liverpool%20Street",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Frankfurt%20%28Main%29%20Hauptbahnhof",
        "Paris%20Gare%20du%20Nord",
        "Brussels%20Midi",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20of%20the%20following%20carbonated%20soft%20drinks%20were%20introduced%20first%3F",
      correct_answer: "Dr.%20Pepper",
      incorrect_answers: ["Coca-Cola", "Sprite", "Mountain%20Dew"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20direction%20does%20the%20Statue%20of%20Liberty%20face%3F",
      correct_answer: "Southeast",
      incorrect_answers: ["Southwest", "Northwest", "Northeast"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20year%20was%20Apple%20Inc.%20founded%3F",
      correct_answer: "1976",
      incorrect_answers: ["1978", "1980", "1974"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "In%20what%20year%20was%20McDonald%27s%20founded%3F",
      correct_answer: "1955",
      incorrect_answers: ["1964", "1951", "1947"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "When%20was%20Hubba%20Bubba%20first%20introduced%3F",
      correct_answer: "1979",
      incorrect_answers: ["1984", "1972", "1980"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20was%20Mountain%20Dew%27s%20original%20slogan%3F",
      correct_answer:
        "Yahoo%21%20Mountain%20Dew...%20It%27ll%20tickle%20your%20innards%21",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Give%20Me%20A%20Dew",
        "Do%20The%20Dew",
        "Get%27%20that%20barefoot%20feelin%27%20drinkin%27%20Mountain%20Dew",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Where%20does%20water%20from%20Poland%20Spring%20water%20bottles%20come%20from%3F",
      correct_answer: "Maine%2C%20United%20States",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Hesse%2C%20Germany",
        "Masovia%2C%20Poland",
        "Bavaria%2C%20Poland",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "When%20did%20the%20website%20%22Facebook%22%20launch%3F",
      correct_answer: "2004",
      incorrect_answers: ["2005", "2003", "2006"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Computer%20manufacturer%20Compaq%20was%20acquired%20for%20%2425%20billion%20dollars%20in%202002%20by%20which%20company%3F",
      correct_answer: "Hewlett-Packard",
      incorrect_answers: ["Toshiba", "Asus", "Dell"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20is%20real%20haggis%20made%20of%3F",
      correct_answer: "Sheep%27s%20Heart%2C%20Liver%20and%20Lungs",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Sheep%27s%20Heart%2C%20Kidneys%20and%20Lungs",
        "Sheep%27s%20Liver%2C%20Kidneys%20and%20Eyes",
        "Whole%20Sheep",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Earl%20Grey%20tea%20is%20black%20tea%20flavoured%20with%20what%3F",
      correct_answer: "Bergamot%20oil",
      incorrect_answers: ["Lavender", "Vanilla", "Honey"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Whose%20greyscale%20face%20is%20on%20the%20kappa%20emoticon%20on%20Twitch%3F",
      correct_answer: "Josh%20DeSeno",
      incorrect_answers: ["Justin%20DeSeno", "John%20DeSeno", "Jimmy%20DeSeno"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20item%20of%20clothing%20is%20usually%20worn%20by%20a%20Scotsman%20at%20a%20wedding%3F",
      correct_answer: "Kilt",
      incorrect_answers: ["Skirt", "Dress", "Rhobes"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20country%20drives%20on%20the%20left%20side%20of%20the%20road%3F",
      correct_answer: "Japan",
      incorrect_answers: ["Germany", "Russia", "China"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "Which%20country%20has%20the%20most%20Trappist%20breweries%3F",
      correct_answer: "Belgium",
      incorrect_answers: ["Netherlands", "France", "USA"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question: "What%20is%20the%20currency%20of%20Poland%3F",
      correct_answer: "Z%C5%82oty",
      incorrect_answers: ["Ruble", "Euro", "Krone"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "In%20ancient%20Greece%2C%20if%20your%20job%20were%20a%20%22hippeus%22%20which%20of%20these%20would%20you%20own%3F",
      correct_answer: "Horse",
      incorrect_answers: ["Weave", "Guitar", "Boat"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Which%20American%20manufactured%20submachine%20gun%20was%20informally%20known%20by%20the%20American%20soldiers%20that%20used%20it%20as%20%22Grease%20Gun%22%3F",
      correct_answer: "M3",
      incorrect_answers: ["Colt%209mm", "Thompson", "MAC-10"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "What%20is%20the%20full%20title%20of%20the%20Prime%20Minister%20of%20the%20UK%3F",
      correct_answer: "First%20Lord%20of%20the%20Treasury",
      incorrect_answers: [
        "Duke%20of%20Cambridge",
        "Her%20Majesty%27s%20Loyal%20Opposition",
        "Manager%20of%20the%20Crown%20Estate",
      ],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "The%20Fields%20Medal%2C%20one%20of%20the%20most%20sought%20after%20awards%20in%20mathematics%2C%20is%20awarded%20every%20how%20many%20years%3F",
      correct_answer: "4",
      incorrect_answers: ["3", "5", "6"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "Linus%20Pauling%2C%20one%20of%20the%20only%20winners%20of%20multiple%20Nobel%20Prizes%2C%20earned%20his%20Nobel%20Prizes%20in%20Chemistry%20and%20what%3F",
      correct_answer: "Peace",
      incorrect_answers: ["Physics", "Economics", "Physiology%2FMedicine"],
    },
    {
      category: "General%20Knowledge",
      type: "multiple",
      difficulty: "medium",
      question:
        "The%20Mexican%20Beer%20%22Corona%22%20is%20what%20type%20of%20beer%3F",
      correct_answer: "Pale%20Lager",
      incorrect_answers: ["India%20Pale%20Ale", "Pilfsner", "Baltic%20Porter"],
    },
  ];